Papers from the Jim Walsh Collection
Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress
- Series 4. Ephemera, 1915-1972, and undated, .21 linear feet
  Included in this series are advertisements for equipment and recordings, newspaper and magazine clippings, newsletters, record catalogs and price lists, and a few miscellaneous items. Researchers are advised to see Series 6 for oversized ephemera.
  Ephemera is arranged alphabetically by genre.
  - Advertisements, 1915-1972 (Box 10, Folder 251)
  - Clippings, 1936, 1952, and undated (Box 10, Folder 252)
    See also Oversized Materials.
  - Newsletters, 1951, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 253)
  - Programs, 1920, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 254)
    Photocopies of 1920 and 1923 programs.
  - Record catalogs and lists, 1900-1901 (Box 10, Folder 255-256)
    Photocopies of 1900-1901 catalogs.
  - Miscellaneous, 1958, and undated (Box 10, Folder 257)
- Series 5. Photographs, 1867-circa 1985, and undated, 1.68 linear feet
  Series 5 consists of approximately 610 photographs of artists and personalities from the early days of recording. Most of the photographs are black and white, but some modern color photographs are included. Many of the photographs are copies (mostly of poor quality) made from earlier prints, books, albums, or posters. Many of the photographs here were used by Walsh to illustrate his columns in Hobbies. Oversized photographs are filed in Series 6.
  Photographs are arranged alphabetically by the name of the person, group or subject. Group, miscellaneous, and unidentified photographs are filed at the end.
  - Alexander, George (Clifford A. Wiley), 1907 (Box 11, Folder 258)
    Copy from 1907 poster.
  - American Quartet, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 259)
    Copy of 1910 photograph.
  - American Singers, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Annand, H. H., 1964 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Arden, Cecil, undated (Box 11, Folder 262)
  - "Arkie" - The Arkansas Woodchopper, undated (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - ASCAP, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 264)
  - Atwood, George, undated (Box 11, Folder 265)
  - Atwood, Harriet, circa 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 266)
  - Baer, Frederic, undated (Box 11, Folder 267)
    Copy.
  - Baker, Elsie (1886-1958), 1948 (Box 11, Folder 268)
  - Banta, Frank E. (1897-1969), undated (Box 11, Folder 269)
  - Barbour, Inez, undated (Box 11, Folder 270)
  - Bard, Wilkie, undated (Box 11, Folder 271)
  - Barrere Trio, undated (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - Bayes, Nora (1880-1928), undated (Box 11, Folder 273)
  - Bell, Digby, undated (Box 11, Folder 274)
  - Belmont, Joseph (1876-1949), 1948 (Box 11, Folder 275)
  - Benoist, André (1879-1953), undated (Box 11, Folder 276)
  - Benzler, Albert, undated (Box 11, Folder 277)
  - Bergy, Ray, undated (Box 11, Folder 278)
  - Berlin, Irving (1888-1989), undated (Box 11, Folder 279)
  - Bieling, John H. (1869-1948), undated (Box 11, Folder 280)
  - Bowman, Charlie, circa 1920-1929 (Box 11, Folder 281)
  - Branscombe, Maud, undated (Box 11, Folder 282)
  - Brown, Albert Edmund, undated (Box 11, Folder 283)
  - Brown, Harry C., undated (Box 11, Folder 284)
  - Bubbles (in blackface), 1930 (Box 11, Folder 285)
  - Bubbles and Ramona, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 286)
  - Bueno, Vincent, undated (Box 11, Folder 287)
  - Burleigh, Harry T., 1939 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - Burr, Henry (Irving Gillette, Harry McClasky), circa 1930-1940 (Box 11, Folder 289)
  - Burt, Leah Brodbeck Stenzel, undated (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - Busch, Lou (Joe “Fingers” Carr), undated (Box 11, Folder 291)
  - Caesar, Irving (1895-1996), undated (Box 11, Folder 292)
  - Cameron, Grace, undated (Box 11, Folder 293)
  - Campbell, Albert and Jack Kaufman, 1926, and undated (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Caruso, Enrico, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 295)
    Copy from 1909 photograph.
  - Case, Anna (1888-1984), undated (Box 11, Folder 296)
  - Chalmers, Thomas, 1915, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - Ciccolini, Guido, 1920 (Box 11, Folder 298)
  - Clarke, Herbert L. (Herbert Lincoln) (1867-1945), undated (Box 11, Folder 299)
  - Clough, Arthur, undated (Box 11, Folder 300)
  - Collins and Harlan, 1922, and undated (Box 11, Folder 301)
    Most are copies.
  - Columbia Stellar Quartette, undated (Box 11, Folder 302)
  - Connolly, Dolly (Mrs. Percy Wenrich), 1911-1921 (Box 11, Folder 303)
  - Cox, Ray, undated (Box 11, Folder 304)
  - Crazy-Elmer, undated (Box 11, Folder 305)
  - Crecent Trio, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 306)
    Copy from 1921 photograph.
  - Cross, Hugh, undated (Box 11, Folder 307)
  - Crumit, Frank with Julia Sanderson, undated (Box 11, Folder 308)
  - Dadum, Royal, undated (Box 11, Folder 309)
  - Dalhart, Vernon (1883-1948), 1921, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 310)
    Copies of 1921 and 1923 photographs.
  - D'Almaine, Charles (1871-1943), 1900 (Box 11, Folder 311)
    Copy of 1900 photograph.
  - Davenport, Edgar L. (1862-1918), undated (Box 11, Folder 312)
  - Davis, Helen, undated (Box 11, Folder 313)
  - Dawson, Peter (1882-1961), undated (Box 11, Folder 314)
  - Dean, Julia (circa 1878-1952), undated, Postcard. (Box 11, Folder 315)
  - De Cisneros, Eleonora, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 316)
  - De Leath, Vaughn, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 317)
  - Denny, Will F. (1860-1908), undated (Box 11, Folder 318)
  - Doherty, James (Jay Clay), undated (Box 11, Folder 319)
  - Doreen, Lilian, undated (Box 11, Folder 320)
  - Dudley, Audley F. and George N., 1913, undated (Box 11, Folder 321)
  - Dudley, S. H., undated (Box 11, Folder 322)
  - Dupree, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 323)
  - Duprez, Fred, undated (Box 11, Folder 324)
  - Eames, Emma (1865-1952), undated (Box 11, Folder 325)
  - Edison Co. staff, equipment, etc., 1890-1919 (Box 11, Folder 326)
    Copies of 1890-1919 photographs.
  - Edison, Thomas A. (Thomas Alva) (1847-1931), undated (Box 11, Folder 327)
  - Edison Group artists, undated (Box 11, Folder 328)
  - Edwards, Gus, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 329)
  - Elliott, G. H.(1882-1962), undated (Box 12, Folder 330)
    Halftone copy.
  - Elman, Mischa (1891-1967), 1958, undated (Box 12, Folder 331)
    One image is a copy.
  - Emerson, Walter, undated (Box 12, Folder 332)
  - Eveready Male Chorus, circa 1927 (Box 12, Folder 333)
  - Eveready Mixed Quartet, circa 1927 (Box 12, Folder 334)
  - Fargo, Milford, undated (Box 12, Folder 335)
  - Farley, James A., undated (Box 12, Folder 336)
  - Farrar, Geraldine (1882-1967), undated (Box 12, Folder 337)
  - Favor, Edward M. (1856-1936), undated (Box 12, Folder 338)
  - Fields, Arthur, circa 1917, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 339)
    One image is a copy of a 1917 photograph.
  - Fields, Gracie, undated (Box 12, Folder 340)
  - Forman, E. C., undated (Box 12, Folder 341)
    RCA sales manager.
  - Formby, George and Luisa Tetrazzini, undated (Box 12, Folder 342)
  - Forsyth, Henry, undated (Box 12, Folder 343)
  - Gambarelli, Maria, undated (Box 12, Folder 344)
  - Gialdini, Guido, undated (Box 12, Folder 345)
  - Girard, Gilbert, 1913 (Box 12, Folder 346)
    Copy of a 1913 photograph.
  - Glenn, Ella Wrenn, undated (Box 12, Folder 347)
  - Glenn, Wilfred, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 348)
    Copy of a 1927 photograph.
  - Greaves, John, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 349)
    Actor.
  - Greaves, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 350)
    Dickens scholar.
  - Green, Abel (1900-1973), undated (Box 12, Folder 351)
  - Greene, Gene, 1912, and undated (Box 12, Folder 352)
  - Gruppe, Paulo M., 1976, undated (Box 12, Folder 353)
  - Hadley, Henry, undated (Box 12, Folder 354)
  - Haydn Quartet (Edison Quartet), undated (Box 12, Folder 355)
  - Hager, Frederick W. (1874-1958), undated (Box 12, Folder 356)
  - Hall, Arthur, undated (Box 12, Folder 357)
  - Hall, Wendell, 1962, undated (Box 12, Folder 358)
  - Handy, W.C. (William Christopher) (1873-1958), undated (Box 12, Folder 359)
  - Hare, Ernest See Jones, Billy
  - Harrington, Fred, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 360)
  - Hart, Chas. (Charles), 1917-1921, 1953, and undated (Box 12, Folder 361)
  - Harvey, Morton, undated (Box 12, Folder 362)
  - Hatfield, Lansing, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 363)
  - Hauk, Minnie (as Carmen), undated (Box 12, Folder 364)
  - Hayes, Bill, undated (Box 12, Folder 365)
  - Helf, Sadie, undated (Box 12, Folder 366)
  - Hemus, Percy, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 367)
    Copy of a 1918 photograph.
  - Henry, Thomas W., undated (Box 12, Folder 368)
  - Hess, Troy, undated (Box 12, Folder 369)
  - Hindermyer, Harvey, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 370)
  - Homer, Louise (1871-1947), undated (Box 12, Folder 371)
  - Hooley, William F. (1861-1918), undated (Box 12, Folder 372)
  - Howard, Joe F., undated (Box 12, Folder 373)
  - Hurtado Brothers Marimba Band, 1940-1941, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 374)
  - James, Lewis, circa 1930 (Box 12, Folder 375)
  - Janis, Elsie (1889-1956), 1938 (Box 12, Folder 376)
  - Jaudas, Eugene, undated (Box 12, Folder 377)
  - John Bieling Days, 1947, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 378)
  - Johnson, Eldridge R., undated (Box 12, Folder 379)
    Photograph of a painting.
  - Johnson, George Washington, undated (Box 12, Folder 380)
  - Jolson, Al (d. 1950), circa 1928, and undated (Box 12, Folder 381)
  - Jones, Ada, undated (Box 12, Folder 382)
  - Jones, Ada and the Shannon Four, 1918 April (Box 12, Folder 383)
  - Jones, Billy (1889-1940) and Ernest Hare, 1925, 1936, and undated (Box 12, Folder 384)
  - Jones, Isham, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 385)
  - Jones, Spike (1911-1965), undated (Box 12, Folder 386)
  - Jordan, Mary (as Aida), undated (Box 12, Folder 387)
  - José, Richard (1862-1941), undated (Box 12, Folder 388)
  - Kaiser, Marie, undated (Box 12, Folder 389)
  - Karle, Theo, undated (Box 12, Folder 390)
  - Kaufman, Irving (1890-1976), 1958, and undated (Box 12, Folder 391)
  - Kaufman, Jack See Campbell, Albert
  - Kelso, Maym (Mary L. Bent), undated (Box 12, Folder 392)
  - Kimmel, John J., 1917 (Box 12, Folder 393)
    Copy of a 1917 photograph.
  - King Oliver’s Creole Jazz Band, undated (Box 12, Folder 394)
  - Kirkby, Stanley, undated (Box 12, Folder 395)
  - Kirkwood, Jack, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 396)
  - Kline, Olive, 1948, and undated (Box 12, Folder 397)
  - Kronold, Hans, undated, Clipping. (Box 12, Folder 398)
  - Lange, Henry, undated (Box 12, Folder 399)
  - Lashanska, Hulda, undated (Box 12, Folder 400)
  - Laska, Edward (1894-1959), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 401)
  - Laurie, Joe, Jr., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 402)
  - Lazzari, Carolina (1891-1946), undated (Box 12, Folder 403)
  - Leavitt, Donald L., undated (Box 12, Folder 404)
  - Lennox, Elizabeth (Box 12, Folder 405)
  - Lennox, Ethel, 1942, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 406)
  - Levy, Jules (1838-1903), undated (Box 12, Folder 407)
  - Lewis, Ted (1892-1971), undated (Box 12, Folder 408)
  - Libbey, J. Aldrich, undated (Box 13, Folder 409)
  - Little Tich (1867-1928), undated (Box 13, Folder 410)
  - Lloyd, Edward (1845-1927), undated (Box 13, Folder 411)
  - Lulu Belle and Scotty, undated (Box 13, Folder 412)
  - Luther, Frank, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 413)
  - Macdonough, Harry (1871-1931), undated (Box 13, Folder 414)
  - Madeira, Addison, undated (Box 13, Folder 415)
  - Mann, Estella Louise (1871-1947), undated (Box 13, Folder 416)
  - Marks, Herb, undated (Box 13, Folder 417)
  - Martin, Frederic, undated (Box 13, Folder 418)
  - Martin, Riccardo, undated (Box 13, Folder 419)
  - Martindale, Jim (James V.) (1894-1981), undated (Box 13, Folder 420)
  - Martinelli, Giovanni (1885-1969), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 421)
  - Mayo, Harry, undated (Box 13, Folder 422)
  - Meader, George Farnham, undated (Box 13, Folder 423)
  - Meeker, Edward (1874-1937), circa 1906 (Box 13, Folder 424)
    Copies from circa 1906 photographs.
  - Melton, James (1904-1961), undated (Box 13, Folder 425)
  - Menefee, Bob, undated (Box 13, Folder 426)
  - Merson, Billy, undated (Box 13, Folder 427)
  - Miller, Christine, undated (Box 13, Folder 428)
  - Miller, Reed (1880-1923) and Frederick Wheeler, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 429)
  - Morgan, Corinne, undated (Box 13, Folder 430)
  - Morphy, Bert, undated (Box 13, Folder 431)
  - Morris, Elida, 1960, and undated (Box 13, Folder 432)
  - Morrisey, Marie, undated (Box 13, Folder 433)
  - Morse, Theodore F. (1873-1924), circa 1910-1924 (Box 13, Folder 434)
  - Morton, Ed, undated (Box 13, Folder 435)
  - Munn, Frank, undated (Box 13, Folder 436)
  - Murray, Billy, undated (Box 13, Folder 437)
  - Murray, Pete, undated (Box 13, Folder 438)
  - Myers, J. W., 1894 (Box 13, Folder 439)
    Photocopy of an 1894 photograph.
  - National Barn Dance (NBC), circa 1939 (Box 13, Folder 440)
  - National Male Quartet, undated (Box 13, Folder 441)
  - Norton, John L., Sr. and Jr. (Woodymay Record Co.), undated (Box 13, Folder 442)
  - Norworth, Jack, undated (Box 13, Folder 443)
  - Oakland, Will (1883-1956), 1931, and undated (Box 13, Folder 444)
    One image is a copy of a 1931 photograph.
  - O’Connor, George (1874-1946), 1943 (Box 13, Folder 445)
  - O’Hara, Geoffrey (1882-1967), 1939, and undated (Box 13, Folder 446)
    One copy of a halftone.
  - Ossman, Vess L., 1923, and undated (Box 13, Folder 447)
  - Parker, Frank, undated (Box 13, Folder 448)
  - Parvis, Taurino (b. 1879), 1907, circa 1910-1919 (Box 13, Folder 449)
    Copies from 1907 and circa 1910-1919 photographs.
  - Peerless Quartet, 1919, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 450)
    Copies of 1919 and 1923 photographs.
  - Phillips, Joseph, undated (Box 13, Folder 451)
  - Phonographs and phonograph dealers, 1910-1912, 1950, and undated (Box 13, Folder 452)
    Three copies of 1910-1912 photographs and two vintage photographs.
  - Piastro, Mishel (1891-1970), undated (Box 13, Folder 453)
  - Polk Miller’s Old South Quartet, undated (Box 13, Folder 454)
  - Pons, Lily (1898-1976), undated (Box 13, Folder 455)
  - Porter, Gene Stratton, circa 1924 (Box 13, Folder 456)
  - Powell, John, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 457)
  - Power, Stella, undated (Box 13, Folder 458)
  - Rea, Virginia, undated (Box 13, Folder 459)
  - Revelers, The, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 460)
    Copy of a 1928 photograph.
  - Rice, Gladys, 1931, and undated (Box 13, Folder 461)
  - Riggs, Quentin, 1966, undated (Box 13, Folder 462)
  - Ring, Blanche, undated (Box 13, Folder 463)
  - Roberts, Bob (1879-1930), undated (Box 13, Folder 464)
  - Robey, George (1869-1954), undated (Box 13, Folder 465)
  - Robinson, Carson, undated (Box 13, Folder 466)
  - Robyn, Willie, undated (Box 13, Folder 467)
  - Rodgers, Richard, undated (Box 13, Folder 468)
  - Rogers, Walter, undated (Box 13, Folder 469)
    Photograph of advertisement.
  - Rollickers, The, circa 1929 (Box 13, Folder 470)
    Copy of a circa 1929 photograph.
  - Romain, Manuel, circa 1915 (Box 13, Folder 471)
    Copies of circa 1915 photographs.
  - Roosevelt, Theodore (1858-1919), 1912 (Box 13, Folder 472)
    Copy of a 1912 photograph.
  - Rose, Eugene, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 473)
  - Rowell, Glenn, undated (Box 13, Folder 474)
  - Sadler, Josie, undated (Box 13, Folder 475)
  - Sanderson, Julia See Crumit, Frank
  - Santley, Charles, Sir (1834-1922), undated (Box 13, Folder 476)
    Photocopy of a magazine page.
  - Scanlan, Walter (Walter Van Brunt), undated (Box 13, Folder 477)
  - Scribner, Jimmy, undated (Box 13, Folder 478)
  - Seltzer, Frank R., undated (Box 13, Folder 479)
    Clipping from booklet.
  - Shannon Four, The, circa 1919 (Box 13, Folder 480)
  - Shaw, Elliott, circa 1915-1920, and undated (Box 13, Folder 481)
    Some items are copies.
  - Shilkret, Nathaniel (1889-1982), 1952 (Box 13, Folder 482)
  - Short, Thomas V. (Thomas Vowler) (1856-1931), undated (Box 13, Folder 483)
  - Simon, Robert, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 484)
  - Smalle, Ed, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 485)
  - Smeck, Roy, undated (Box 13, Folder 486)
  - Spalding, Albert (1888-1953), 1916, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 487)
  - Spencer, Harry, undated (Box 13, Folder 488)
  - Spencer, Len (1867-1914), 1867, 1958, and undated (Box 13, Folder 489)
    Includes a silhouette.
  - Stanley, Aileen (1893-1982) and Bill Murray, undated (Box 13, Folder 490)
    Photograph of a 1926 program.
  - Steele, Dora (Dowdy), undated (Box 13, Folder 491)
  - Sterling, Louis, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 492)
    Copy negative from a 1948 photograph.
  - Stevens, Ernest L., undated (Box 13, Folder 493)
    Photograph of an advertisement.
  - Sundelius, Marie, undated (Box 14, Folder 494)
  - Superba Musical Comedy Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 495)
  - Talking Machine Jobbers, National Association, 1914, 1922, and undated (Box 14, Folder 496)
    One image is a copy of a 1914 photograph.
  - Taylor, Deems (1885-1966), undated (Box 14, Folder 497)
  - "Thanks to the Yanks" program (WABC-CBS), undated (Box 14, Folder 498)
  - Thompson, William H., undated (Box 14, Folder 499)
  - Tierney, Harry (1890-1965), 1939 (Box 14, Folder 500)
  - Tilley, Vesta, 1906 (Box 14, Folder 501)
  - Tiny Tim with Jim Walsh, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 502)
  - Tollefsen Trio, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 503)
    Copies of 1916 photographs.
  - Trix, Helen, 1907 (Box 14, Folder 504)
    Copies of 1907 photographs.
  - Turner, Eva, Dame (1892-1990), undated (Box 14, Folder 505)
  - Ukranian National Chorus, undated, Postcard. (Box 14, Folder 506)
  - Urlus, Jacques, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 507)
  - Van, Gus (1887-1968), undated (Box 14, Folder 508)
  - Van Eps, Fred (1878-1960), 1955, and undated (Box 14, Folder 509)
  - Van Eps Quartet, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 510)
    Copy of a 1920 photograph.
  - Van Eps Trio, circa 1919 (Box 14, Folder 511)
  - Victor Orchestra, circa 1907 (Box 14, Folder 512)
    Copy of a circa 1907 photograph.
  - Victor Talking Machine Co., 1901, 1919, and undated (Box 14, Folder 513)
    Some images are copies of 1901 and 1919 photographs.
  - Victor recording artists dinner, New York, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 514)
  - Voorhees, Donald, 1964, and undated (Box 14, Folder 515)
  - Walker, Ray, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 516)
  - Walsh, Arthur, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 517)
  - Walsh, Jim (1903-1990), circa 1939-circa 1985 (Box 14, Folder 518-520)
  - Walsh's Wax Works, (WDBJ, Roanoke, Virginia), circa 1944-circa 1949 (Box 14, Folder 521)
  - Watahwaso, Princess, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 522)
  - Wenrich, Percy (1887-1952), 1939 (Box 14, Folder 523)
  - Wheeler, Elizabeth and William, circa 1913, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 524)
  - Wheeler, Fred (James F. Harrison), undated (Box 14, Folder 525)
    See also Miller, Reed.
  - White, Edna (b. 1892), 1912, 1922, 1949, 1974, 1978, and undated (Box 14, Folder 526)
    Three images are copies of 1912 and 1922 photographs.
  - Whitehouse, Fred, undated (Box 14, Folder 527)
  - Whiteman, Paul (1890-1967), undated (Box 14, Folder 528)
  - Whiting, Richard A. (1891-1938), undated (Box 14, Folder 529)
  - Whitney, Edwin M., undated (Box 14, Folder 530)
  - Wiedoeft, Rudy, 1918-1932 (Box 14, Folder 531)
  - Wilder, Marshall, undated (Box 14, Folder 532)
  - Williams, Bert (1874-1922), undated (Box 14, Folder 533)
  - Williams, Billy, undated (Box 14, Folder 534)
  - Williams, Emlyn (1905-1987), 1952 (Box 14, Folder 535)
  - Wills, Nat M., undated (Box 14, Folder 536)
  - WJHL staff, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 537)
  - Woodymay Record Co., 1945, and undated (Box 14, Folder 538)
  - Wreck of the Old 97, 1952, and undated (Box 14, Folder 539)
    Landscape, survivor, etc.
  - WSLS-FM community sing, undated (Box 14, Folder 540)
  - Youmans, Vincent (1898-1946), 1939 (Box 14, Folder 541)
  - Young, John (Harry Anthony), undated (Box 14, Folder 542)
  - Young, Victor (1889-1968), undated (Box 14, Folder 543)
  - Miscellaneous recording artists: groups and composites, circa 1940-circa 1960, and undated (Box 14, Folder 544-545)
  - Unidentified individuals, undated (Box 14, Folder 546)
- Series 6. Oversized Materials, 1914-1953, and undated, 1.2 linear feet
  Oversized poster in map case is stored separately. Advance notice is required for viewing; contact a reference librarian in the Recorded Sound Reference Center, Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress, Washington, DC, 20540-4690; (202) 707-7833.
  Oversized materials consist of advertisements, newspaper and magazine clippings, scrapbook photocopies, a record sleeve, miscellaneous artwork, photographs, and a poster. A series of stand-up cardboard advertising figures is included; personalities depicted are Victor Herbert, Irene Bordoni, Georgie Price, Fannie Brice, Will Rogers, Ernestine Schumann-Heink, Tito Schipa, Luisa Tetrazzini, and Titta Ruffo. Artwork consists of a cartoon panel signed by Jimmy Hatlo, a (poor) reproduction of the painting The Firstborn by Fagan, and a drawing of Mostar, Bosnia, by Josh Newman. A record sleeve from a Theodore Roosevelt address recorded in 1913 can also be found in this series. Oversized photocopies of a scrapbook with clippings on Charley Case are in the final folder. One oversized poster entitled Some Columbia Talent, features photographs of various recording artists.
  Oversized materials are arranged alphabetically by type.
  - Advertisements, 1914, 1925, and undated (Box 15, Folder 547)
  - Advertising figures, undated (Box 15, Folder 548-549)
  - Artwork, miscellaneous, 1953, and undated (Box 15, Folder 550)
  - Clippings, 1890, 1914-1916, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 551)
    Includes photocopies.
  - Photographs of individuals
    - Baker, Elsie (1886-1958), undated (Box 15, Folder 552)
    - Caruso and Ruffo, undated (Box 15, Folder 552)
    - Farley, James A., undated (Box 15, Folder 552)
    - Farrar, Geraldine (1882-1967), undated (Box 15, Folder 552)
    - Dewey, Thomas E. (Thomas Edmund) (1902-1971), 1948 (Box 15, Folder 552)
    - Merman, Ethel, undated (Box 15, Folder 552)
      Magazine portrait.
    - Oakland, Will, undated (Box 15, Folder 552)
      Billboard advertisement for Hunter Island Inn.
    - Unidentified woman, undated (Box 15, Folder 552)
  - Photographs: Victor Talking Machine Printed Artist
    Photographs (with album lists).
    - Bori, Lucrezia, 1924-1925 (Box 15, Folder 553)
    - Chemet, Renée, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 553)
    - Flonzaley Quartet, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 553)
    - Gogorza, Emilio de, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 553)
    - Marsh, Lucy Isabelle, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 553)
    - McCormack, John, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 553)
  - Photographs: groups and composites
    - The Victor Male Chorus, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 554)
    - Edison dealers' banquet at the Waldorf-Astoria, undated (Box 15, Folder 554)
    - The Friar’s Frolic, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 554)
    - Red Cross benefit concert, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 554)
      Songwriters, artists, and composers. Copy.
    - Miscellaneous, unidentified, undated (Box 15, Folder 554)
  - Seltzer, Frank R., undated (Box 15, Folder 479)
  - Record sleeve: "A Message by Theodore Roosevelt in His Own Voice," circa 1937 (Box 15, Folder 555)
    Reeves Sound Studio; original dictated in 1913.
  - Scrapbook pages: copies of clippings related to Charley Case, 1906-1916 (Box 15, Folder 556)
  - Poster: Some Columbia talent, circa 1900-circa 1910 (Oversize map case)
- Series 7. Scrapbooks, 1892-1939, and undated, 2.5 linear feet
  Scrapbooks are arranged according to size and preservation needs.
  - Recording index, undated (Box 16, Folder 557)
    Arranged by artist name.
    From binder.
  - Scrapbook: Newspaper and magazine clippings on artists and recordings, circa 1920-circa 1939 (Box 16, Folder 558)
  - Scrapbook: Newspaper and magazine clippings on artists and recordings, circa 1915-circa 1939 (Box 16, Folder 559)
  - Scrapbook: Newspaper and magazine clippings and advertisements, 1892-1925 (Box 16, Folder 560)
  - Scrapbooks: Correspondence between Charles W. Carson and Columbia Phonograph Co. concerning his recordings in Mexico, China, and Japan, 1904-1907, 2 volumes. (Box 17, Folder 561-562)
  - Scrapbook: "Descriptive Catalogue ... Wonder Double Bell Talking Machine" and several Talk-o-Phone advertisements, undated (Box 17, Folder 562)
- Series 8. Bound Publications, 1901-1977, and undated, 14 linear feet